(520) 360 - 3373 relero90@gmail.com Denver, CO

Becca Roberts < SOFTWARE DEVELOPER />

LinkedIn.com/becca-roberts github.com/relero90/ Professional Portfolio

Software developer with a passion for collaboration, creative problem-solving, and continued personal and professional growth. Nine years of elementary classroom teaching have taught me to be adaptable, organized, self-sufficient, and kind. Three months of 60-hour weeks in the <u>University of Denver's Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp</u> have prepared me to thrive in a fast-paced, outcomes-driven, agile environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

React JS | Node.js | npm | Express JS | MySQL/Workbench | MongoDB/Compass | GraphQL/Apollo HTML5 | CSS3/Bootstrap | JavaScript/jQuery | REST | Handlebars

PROJECTS

BUBBLE ARCADE | Software Developer | GitHub | 2022

- Delivered ReactJS application with self-contained, reusable components.
- Developed and designed style and theme of the application for a consistent UX.
- Retrieved data from GraphQL API using an Apollo client.
- Coordinated a full-stack team to deploy the project to Heroku in five days.

KISS THE COOK | Scrum Master & Lead Software Developer | GitHub | 2022

- Led daily team stand-ups and developer check-ins.
- Conceptualized and developed app from wire frame and relational modeling to a visually-appealing UI built on a RESTful API built using Node.js and Express
- Learned and implemented express-session for user authentication.
- Contributed to enhanced user interaction using JavaScript.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK CODING CERTIFICATE <u>University of Denver Bootcamps</u>	OCT 2022
MASTER OF EDUCATION with Distinction Northern Arizona University	DEC 2013
BACHELOR OF THE ARTS with concentration in Biology and Environmental Studies Colgate University	MAY 2012

WORK EXPERIENCE

TEACHER'S ASSISTANT	NOV 2022 –
2U Front-End Development Bootcamp	PRESENT
	and the second s

Lead small-group instruction for adult learners in front-end JavaScript, HTML, and CSS

TEACHER – 4TH GRADE | Instructional Leadership Team (2020-22)

Westgate Elementary School, Jeffco Public Schools

JUL 2019 –

JUL 2022

 Adapted and transitioned to meeting data-driven student outcomes while teaching fully remotely for the 2020-2021 school year.

TEACHER – 3RD GRADE | School Advisory Board (2018-19) | School Restart Design Team (2017-18) AUG 2016 -John H. Amesse Elementary School, Denver Public Schools JUL 2019 Adopted a leadership position amongst my peers by volunteering as the building-level Association Representative for the Denver Classroom Teachers Association (2018-2019) TEACHER – ECE-5TH Science, Technology, Engineering, and Math (STEM) JUL 2015 -Oakland Elementary School, Denver Public Schools JUL 2016 • First encountered programming through my 5th grade robotics unit focusing on "if" conditionals for the safe cleanup of the Fukushima nuclear disaster. TEACHER – K-3RD Science, Technology, Engineering, and Math (STEM) JUL 2014 -Pine Lane Elementary School, Douglas County School District JUL 2015

• Independently enriched a single month-long unit of a provided curriculum to span an entire school year and connect and engage appropriately with students across multiple grade levels.